export const chapter = "Chapter -20: Essay Writing";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What does television combine to provide information?",
          optionA: "Taste and Smell",
          optionB: "Sight and Sound",
          optionC: "Touch and Hearing",
          correctAnswer: "Sight and Sound",
        },
        {
          question: "How is television described in the text?",
          optionA: "A curse of science",
          optionB: "A source of knowledge",
          optionC: "An obstacle to education",
          correctAnswer: "A source of knowledge",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is mentioned as a part of mass communication in the text?",
          optionA: "Mobile Phones",
          optionB: "Television",
          optionC: "Telegraph",
          correctAnswer: "Television",
        },
        {
          question:
            "According to the passage, what does a soldier do in forests, mountains, and deserts?",
          optionA: "Gardening",
          optionB: "Tough Training",
          optionC: "Cooking",
          correctAnswer: "Tough Training",
        },
        {
          question: "Why does a soldier sacrifice his life, as per the text?",
          optionA: "For a luxurious life",
          optionB: "For the safety of the country",
          optionC: "For personal gain",
          correctAnswer: "For the safety of the country",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Who is described as wearing a simple but attractive saree-blouse?",
          optionA: "Television",
          optionB: "A soldier",
          optionC: "Ms. Malti",
          correctAnswer: "Ms. Malti",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does Ms. Malti teach in addition to academic subjects?",
          optionA: "Dancing",
          optionB: "Good Manners",
          optionC: "Painting",
          correctAnswer: "Good Manners",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the role of teachers, according to the passage?",
          optionA: "To create problems",
          optionB: "To make students unsuccessful",
          optionC: "To help students become able and successful people",
          correctAnswer: "To help students become able and successful people",
        },
        {
          question:
            "According to the text, how does television contribute to increasing general knowledge?",
          optionA: "Through cooking shows",
          optionB: "Through news",
          optionC: "Through fashion shows",
          correctAnswer: "Through news",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How does the text suggest one can gather knowledge by using television?",
          optionA: "By visiting libraries",
          optionB: "By sitting at home and watching",
          optionC: "By attending seminars",
          correctAnswer: "By sitting at home and watching",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Television is considered a blessing of ___________.",
          optionA: "Nature",
          optionB: "Science",
          optionC: "Mathematics",
          correctAnswer: "Science",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Television combines both ________ and ________ to provide information.",
          optionA: "Taste, Smell",
          optionB: "Sight, Sound",
          optionC: "Touch, Hearing",
          correctAnswer: "Sight, Sound",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Through television, businessmen and owners of big companies inform people about their __________ goods.",
          optionA: "Used",
          optionB: "Launched",
          optionC: "Expensive",
          correctAnswer: "Launched",
        },
        {
          question: "A soldier often sacrifices his life for our __________.",
          optionA: "Entertainment",
          optionB: "Safety",
          optionC: "Education",
          correctAnswer: "Safety",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A soldier undergoes tough training and has to live in forests, mountains, and __________.",
          optionA: "Oceans",
          optionB: "Valleys",
          optionC: "Deserts",
          correctAnswer: "Deserts",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ms. Malti, the teacher, is described as wearing a simple but attractive __________.",
          optionA: "Suit",
          optionB: "Skirt",
          optionC: "Saree-blouse",
          correctAnswer: "Saree-blouse",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Teachers help us become able and successful people by teaching us __________.",
          optionA: "Science only",
          optionB: "Dedicatedly",
          optionC: "Only theoretical concepts",
          correctAnswer: "Dedicatedly",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ms. Malti teaches us good manners and how to study and learn __________.",
          optionA: "Quickly",
          optionB: "Well",
          optionC: "Lazily",
          correctAnswer: "Well",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Television has become the best source of __________, according to the text.",
          optionA: "Money",
          optionB: "Knowledge",
          optionC: "Happiness",
          correctAnswer: "Knowledge",
        },
        {
          question: "A soldier keeps vigil on our borders in __________.",
          optionA: "Cities",
          optionB: "Towns",
          optionC: "Forests, mountains, and deserts",
          correctAnswer: "Forests, mountains, and deserts",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "Television combines both sight and sound.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A soldier often sacrifices his life for entertainment.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ms. Malti, the teacher, is described as wearing a complex outfit.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Teachers only focus on theoretical concepts.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Descriptive writing in the context of the text involves creating a mental image with words.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Television is considered a curse of science.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "A soldier keeps vigil on borders in cities only.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Pictorial representations in ancient writing systems remained unchanged over time.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Television is described as an obstacle to education.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A soldier undergoes tough training in forests, mountains, and oceans.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
